A Finding Aid to the Architectural League of New York Records, 1880s-1974, bulk 1927-1968, in the Archives of American Art AAA.archleag
Archives of American Art
- Functions and Events, 1909, 1931-1973; Series 6; 9.35 Linear feet Boxes 84-9, OV 120
  - League-Sponsored Functions and Events, 1909, 1931-1973; 6.1
    - 1952 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 86)
      - Austrian Dinner (Oct. 23, 1952), (2 folders) (Box 86, Folder 29-30)
      - Roman Evening (Nov. 20, 1952), (2 folders) (Box 86, Folder 31-32)
      - Christmas Fund for Employees, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 33)
      - Christmas Party (Dec. 22, 1952), 1952-1953 (Box 86, Folder 34)
    - 1953 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 86)
      - Blood Donor Program, 1953 (Box 86, Folder 35)
      - Christmas Luncheons, 1953-1962 (Box 86, Folder 36)
      - Forum Buffet Suppers, 1953 (Box 86, Folder 37)
      - Past Presidents Exhibition, 1953 (Box 86, Folder 38)
      - "Classical Landscape Without Figures," Dinner and Slides, Frederick Woodbridge Evening (Jan. 22, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 39)
      - League Dinner Smorgasbord (Mar. 11, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 40)
      - National Gold Medal Exhibition, Final Dinner (Mar. 19, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 41)
      - League Inaugural Dinner (Apr. 9, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 42)
      - League Inaugural Dinner, Invitations (Apr. 9, 1953), (8 folders) (Box 86, Folder 43-50)
      - Lift Slab Luncheon (May 22, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 51)
      - Birch Burdette Long Buffet Supper (June 4, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 52)
      - Garden Party (June 16, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 53)
      - General Membership Meeting (June 30, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 54)
      - "An Evening in Switzerland" (Sept. 17, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 55)
      - Cocktail Party (Oct. 1, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 56)
      - "Status of the Arts at Mid-Century" (Oct. 8, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 57)
      - Brunner Award Cocktail Party, Hugh Ferriss (Nov. 2, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 58)
      - "Inter-relation of Architecture and Engineering" (Nov. 12, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 59)
      - Public Housing Dinner and Meeting, H. Myers Award Presented to Lewis Mumford (Nov. 24, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 60)
      - Puerto Rican and Caribbean Architecture (Dec. 3, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 61)
      - Puerto Rico and Caribbean Evening, Dinner (Dec. 3, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 62)
      - "Commerce as a Patron of the Arts" (Dec. 10, 1953) (Box 86, Folder 63)
      - Christmas Party (Dec. 23, 1953), 1953-1954 (Box 86, Folder 64)
    - 1954 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 86)
      - "Technical Development and Its Impact on Architectural Esthetics" (Jan. 14, 1954), 1953-1954 (Box 86, Folder 65)
      - Henry Hering Dedication Luncheon (Jan. 22, 1954) (Box 86, Folder 66)
      - General Membership Meeting (Jan. 28, 1954), 1953-1954 (Box 86, Folder 67)
      - Indian Evening, Hildreth Meiere (Feb. 4, 1954) (Box 86, Folder 68)
      - "Technical Development and Its Impact on Painting" (Feb. 11, 1954), 1953-1954 (Box 86, Folder 69)
      - Mississippi Steamboat Party (Feb. 19, 1954) (Box 86, Folder 70)
      - "The Architectures of North Africa," G.E. Kidder Smith (Mar. 4, 1954), 1953-1954 (Box 86, Folder 71)
      - "Technical Development and Its Impact on Sculpture" (Mar. 11, 1954), 1953-1954 (Box 86, Folder 72)
      - National Gold Medal Dinner (Mar. 18, 1954) (Box 86, Folder 73)
      - "Summation, Future Directions and Changes" (Apr. 8, 1954), 1953-1954 (Box 86, Folder 74)
    - 1954 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 87)
      - Inaugural Dinner (Apr. 22, 1954), 1951, 1954 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - "Environment and Anonymous Architecture," Sibyl Moholy-Nagy (May 27, 1954) (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Cuban Dinner (Oct. 6, 1954) (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - B.A.I.D. and League Paris Prize Dinner (Oct. 28, 1954) (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Honorary and Members Dinner, Replies (Dec. 9, 1954) (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Christmas Party (Dec. 23, 1954) (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - 1955 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 87)
      - Demonstration Luncheon, 1955 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Educational Forums, Copies of Brochures of Previous Series, 1955-1957 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - League Blood Bank, 1955 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - National Gold Medal Exhibition Dinner, 1955-1956 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - Hildreth Meiere Evening, Dinner and Film (Feb. 10, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Harvey Wiley Corbett Memorial Exhibition and Dinner (Feb. 17, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - National Gold Medal Dinner (Mar. 17, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - Lewis G. Adams Maya Architecture Evening (Mar. 31, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - Circus Party, A.I.A, B.A.I.D., Arch. League (Apr. 15, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Jan Juta Portugal Evening (Apr. 28, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - Joint Forum Dinner, A.I.A. NY Chapter, Municipal Arts Society, Arch League (May 10, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - Cocktail Party-Helen Treadwell, Messrs Adams, Woodbridge and Glinsky (June 1, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 18)
      - Stained Glass and Mosaics Luncheon (June 2, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 19)
      - League Outing (June 4, 1955), 1954-1955 (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - Avery Award Dinner, Correspondence and Releases (Oct. 25, 1955), 1955-1956 (Box 87, Folder 21)
      - New Members Exhibition and Party (Oct. 25, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 22)
      - "Gab Fest Evening" League Dinner (Nov. 17, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 23)
      - "Heads, Horns and Hoofing," Walter Kilham, Jr. (Dec. 8, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 24)
      - Christmas Luncheon (Dec. 22, 1955) (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - 1956 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 87)
      - A.I.A. and League Joint Luncheon (Professor Werner Hebebrand), 1956 (Box 87, Folder 26)
      - Christmas Party, Jack Lenor Larson, Decorating Committee Chairman (1956), 1955-1963 (Box 87, Folder 27)
      - Demonstration Luncheon Series, 1956 (Box 87, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous Events in Connection With 75th Anniversary of the League, 1956-1957 (Box 87, Folder 29)
      - New Attitudes Forum, Discussion and Demonstration Series, 1956-1957 (Box 87, Folder 30)
      - League Inaugural Dinner Annual Business Meeting (Apr. 5, 1956) (Box 87, Folder 31)
      - 75th Anniversary Dinner (May 3, 1956), 1956-1957; (5 folders) (Box 87, Folder 32-36)
      - Fall Outing, General Foods and Standard Vacuum Oil (Nov. 10, 1956) (Box 87, Folder 37)
      - The Henry O. Avery Award Dinner (Nov. 30, 1956) (Box 87, Folder 38)
      - Luncheon: Debate - Classical vs. Romantic, Hugh Ferriss, Moderator (Dec. 13, 1956) (Box 87, Folder 39)
      - Hildreth Meiere's Evening and Dinner: Egypt, Jordan and Lebanon (Dec. 14, 1956), 1956-1957 (Box 87, Folder 40)
      - New Members Cocktail Party (With Miss Meire's Film Showing) (Dec. 14, 1956) (Box 87, Folder 41)
    - 1957 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 87)
      - Blood Donor Program, 1957-1959 (Box 87, Folder 42)
      - "White Sheep of Denali" at the American Museum of Natural History, Walter H. Kilham, Jr. (Feb. 27, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 43)
      - 75th Anniversary Inaugural Dinner and Dance (Mar. 21, 1957), 1957-1958 (Box 87, Folder 44)
      - Julian Clarence Levi Testimonial Dinner (May 3, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 45)
      - Luncheon: Sir Hugh Casson, "Campus Planning in England" (May 21, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 46)
      - G.E. Kidder Smith Evening, Dinner and Slides (May 23, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 47)
      - Informal Evening With Prof. Schmerz (June 26, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 48)
      - League Dinner - Slides by James Padavic (Sept. 12, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 49)
      - Luncheon: Peter Smithson, "The New Brutalism" (Oct. 1, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 50)
      - "An Evening With Mies van der Rohe," Correspondence (Oct. 3, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 51)
      - Luncheon: Paul Nelson, "New Humanism in Architecture" (Oct. 8, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 52)
      - Luncheon: Betty Pepis, "The Triennale and Berlin Arch" (Oct. 17, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 53)
      - Fulbright Scholarship Award Winners Luncheon, #1 (Nov. 7, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 54)
      - Seagram Building Tour, George A. Fuller Co. Luncheon Host (Nov. 9, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 55)
      - Puerto Rican Evening, Jose A. Fernandez, Chairman (Nov. 14, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 56)
      - Christmas Party (Dec. 19, 1957) (Box 87, Folder 57)
    - 1958 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 88)
      - State Department Exhibition Dinner, Correspondence (Jan. 9, 1958), 1957-1958 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Henry O. Avery Prize for Small Sculpture, Dinner (Jan. 23, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - Marco Polo Dinner Dance, Mr. Fernandez, Chairman (Feb. 7, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - Walter Kilham Evening, "Musk Oxen and Free Gold" (Feb. 20, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Helen Treadwell Evening, Slides of Dubrovnik (Mar. 6, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - UNESCO Evening With Marcel Breuer (Mar. 20, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - National Gold Medal Dinner (Mar. 27, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - League Inaugural Dinner (New Members Cocktail Party) (Apr. 10, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - League Inaugural Dinner Speeches (Apr. 10, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 9)
      - Hildreth Meiere Dinner and Slides (Apr. 24, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 10)
      - Regional Residential Architecture Exhibit and Dinner (May 8, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 11)
      - Frederick J. Woodbridge Evening Dinner, Also Freidsam Medal Award, (May 15, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 12)
      - "A Visit to the Brussels World's Fair" Dinner and Talk (June 12, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - "Collaboration of the Building Arts: Shopping Centers" (Sept. 4, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 14)
      - League Outing, Mr. Pahlmann, Chairman (Sept. 27, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 15)
      - "The Photography of Architecture," Dinner (Oct. 9, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 16)
      - "Murals in New York's Public Schools" (Oct. 23, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 17)
      - "The Origins of Abstract Architecture" (Nov. 13, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 18)
      - "Architecture: Puerto Rico, Old and New" (Nov. 20, 1958), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 19)
      - "Talk on Russia," Justice Douglas (Dec. 4, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 20)
      - Travelogue, Turkish Evening, Betti Richard (Dec. 4, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 21)
      - "Sculpture: The Work of Constantino Nivola" (Dec. 11, 1958), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 22)
      - Christmas Party (Dec. 23, 1958) (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - 1959 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 88)
      - "What is Your Taste in Architecture" (Jan. 8, 1959), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 24)
      - "Landscape Design: The Work of Dan Kiley," [Exhibit] Jan. 19-30, Dinner (Jan. 22, 1959), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 25)
      - "Space Planning in the Time Life Building" (Feb. 5, 1959), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 26)
      - "Craftsmanship: The Ceiling - Forms and Textures" (Feb. 26, 1959) (Box 88, Folder 27)
      - "Craftsmanship in Religious Architecture" (Mar. 12, 1959), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 28)
      - "Engineering: The Work of Pier Luigi Nevi" (Mar. 26, 1959) (Box 88, Folder 29)
      - "Today's Architecture" (Apr. 2, 1959), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 30)
      - League Inaugural Dinner and Annual Meeting (Apr. 8, 1959) (Box 88, Folder 31)
      - "Students' Work in Building Arts" (Apr. 23, 1959), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 32)
      - "Lighting as a Tool of Architecture" (May 14, 1959), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 33)
      - "Architecture: The Work of Minoru Yamasaki" Dinner (May 21, 1959) (Box 88, Folder 34)
      - "The Work of Younger Architects" (June 11, 1959), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 35)
      - Travelogue (June 18, 1959), 1958-1959 (Box 88, Folder 36)
      - Fall Outing, Long Island Tour (Oct. 8, 1959) (Box 88, Folder 37)
      - Metropolitan Opera House Tours (Metour) (Dec. 1, 1959 and Jan. 5, 1960), 1959-1960 (Box 88, Folder 38)
    - 1960 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 88)
      - "New Forces in Architecture", 1960-1961; (2 folders) (Box 88, Folder 39-40)
      - National Gold Medal Exhibition of the Building Arts, Speeches (Feb. 11, 1960) (Box 88, Folder 41)
      - Awards Dinner, Avery, B.B. Long, and Howard Myers (Mar. 24, 1960) (Box 88, Folder 42)
      - League Inaugural Dinner, Freidsam Award and Gold Medal Awards (Apr. 7, 1960) (Box 88, Folder 43)
      - Student's Evening (Apr. 28, 1960) (Box 88, Folder 44)
      - "Austria and South Germany," Travelogue by Philip Bartlett (May 26, 1960) (Box 88, Folder 45)
      - League Summer Outing, Old Westbury Gardens (July 23, 1960) (Box 88, Folder 46)
      - League Dinner and Lecture Series (Oct. 27, 1960), 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 47)
      - Flamenco!, League Social Evening (Nov. 10, 1960) (Box 88, Folder 48)
    - 1961 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 89)
      - "The Building Room: Architecture in Decline," List of Subscribers to the Forum Series, 1961; (2 folders) (Box 89, Folder 1-2)
      - Japanese Evening, Jose A. Fernandez, Chairman (Jan. 26, 1961) (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Hawaiian Evening and Costume Party (Mar. 10, 1961) (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Walter Kilham Evening Dinner (Apr. 6, 1961) (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - New Members Cocktail Party and Exhibition (Apr. 13, 1961), (2 folders) (Box 89, Folder 6-7)
      - Columbia Testimonial Dinner - LeCorbusier, Walter Gropius, Mies van der Rohe, Frank Lloyd Wright (May 1, 1961) (Box 89, Folder 8)
      - "The Lively Arts and the Building Arts," The Dramatic Workshop Repertory Theatre (Oct. 6, 1961), 1960-1961 (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - Christmas Luncheon (Dec. 21, 1961), 1942, 1958-1961 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - 1962 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 89)
      - Installation of Robert Allan Jacobs as President, Remarks by Julian C. Levi (Apr. 5, 1962) (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - Dinner in Honor of Julian C. Levi (Sept. 30), circa 1962 (Box 89, Folder 12)
      - Chester B. Price Sketch Dinner (Nov. 16, 1962) (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - 1963 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 89)
      - "The New Federal Architecture" Dinner and Lecture (Mar. 14, 1963) (Box 89, Folder 14)
      - "Echoes of Paris," Jose A. Fernandez, Chairman (Apr. 5, 1963) (Box 89, Folder 15)
      - "Architects and Sculptors: Collaborators or Competitors?" (Apr. 18, 1963) (Box 89, Folder 16)
      - Armenian Architecture Lecture, Edouard Utudjian (May 28, 1963) (Box 89, Folder 17)
      - Annual Members Show Cocktail Party, Minor Bishop, Executive Committee Chairman (Sept. 17, 1963) (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - 1964 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 89)
      - Current Work Memoranda, Wednesdays at the League, 1964-1965 (Box 89, Folder 19)
      - Friday Night Seminars, 1964-1965 (Box 89, Folder 20)
      - Thursday Night Affairs, 1964-1965 (Box 89, Folder 21)
      - Spring Outing, Yale University Eero Saarinen Complex (May 23, 1964) (Box 89, Folder 22)
      - League Inaugural Dinner and Awards [And Other Miscellaneous League Events] (May 27, 1964), 1964-1965 (Box 89, Folder 23)
      - "The New Challenge of Public Architecture" (Dec. 3, 1964) (Box 89, Folder 24)
      - Christmas Party (Dec. 22, 1964), 1963-1964 (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - 1965 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 89)
      - Museum of Modern Art Lecture Series, Bills and Cost, 1965-1966 (Box 89, Folder 26)
      - Architectural League and National Society of Mural Painters, "Byzantine Décor and Its Place" (Feb. 4, 1965) (Box 89, Folder 27)
      - Annual Luncheon Meeting (Apr. 15, 1965) (Box 89, Folder 28)
      - Spring Outing, Phoenix Mutual Insurance Co. with Max Abromovitz (May 8, 1965) (Box 89, Folder 29)
      - Inaugural Dinner and Awards (May 26, 1965) (Box 89, Folder 30)
      - Julian Clarence Levi 60th Anniversary Cocktail Party (Sept. 30, 1965) (Box 89, Folder 31)
      - Julian C. Levi Summer Members Show and Dinner (Sept. 30, 1965) (Box 89, Folder 32)
      - Richard Neutra Evening (Nov. 17, 1965) (Box 89, Folder 33)
      - Christmas Luncheon (Dec. 21, 1965) (Box 89, Folder 34)
    - 1966 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 89)
      - "The Shape of Cities in Our Time" Spring Series, 1965-1966; (3 folders) (Box 89, Folder 35-37)
      - President's Medal Presentation Dinner Honoring Kenzo Tange (Mar. 24, 1966) (Box 89, Folder 38)
      - Inaugural Dinner and Awards (May 19, 1966) (Box 89, Folder 39)
      - Executive Committee Meeting and Luncheon (Oct. 4, 1966) (Box 89, Folder 40)
    - 1967 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 89)
      - "Dinners for 36," General, circa 1967-1969 (Box 89, Folder 41)
      - "Dinners for 36, #1," Helen Treadwell (Mar. 30, 1967) (Box 89, Folder 42)
      - "Dinners for 36, #2," Walter Kilham (May 3, 1967) (Box 89, Folder 43)
      - "Dinners for 36, #3," Charles Middeleer (June 22, 1967) (Box 89, Folder 44)
      - "Dinners for 36, #4," Bill and Maggie Field (July 27, 1967) (Box 89, Folder 45)
      - "Dinners for 36, #5," Edgar I. Williams (Oct. 3, 1967) (Box 89, Folder 46)
      - "Dinners for 36, #6," Roy Moyer (Nov. 9, 1967) (Box 89, Folder 47)
      - Julian C. Levi 93rd Birthday Party (Dec. 8, 1967) (Box 89, Folder 48)
      - Christmas Party, House Committee, Correspondence (Dec. 19, 1967), 1966-1967 (Box 89, Folder 49)
    - 1968 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 89)
      - "Dinners for 36, #7," Alton S. Tobey (Jan. 11, 1968) (Box 89, Folder 50)
      - Poetry Series (Jan. 24 - Apr. 10, 1968) (Box 89, Folder 51)
      - "Dinners for 36, #8," Martin Andrews (Feb. 8, 1968) (Box 89, Folder 52)
      - "Dinners for 36, #9," George E. Kidder Smith (Mar. 6, 1968) (Box 89, Folder 53)
      - "Dinners for 36, #10," David Kenneth Specter (Mar. 27, 1968) (Box 89, Folder 54)
      - "Dinners for 36, #11," Color Slide Competition (Apr. 24, 1968) (Box 89, Folder 55)
      - Television Series, Les Levine (Apr. 25 - May 16, 1968) (Box 89, Folder 56)
      - "Dinners for 36, #12," Myron Goldfinger (Aug. 15, 1968) (Box 89, Folder 57)
      - "Dinners for 36, #13," Tim Prentice (Oct. 24, 1968) (Box 89, Folder 58)
      - Julian C. Levi's 94th Birthday Party (Dec. 9, 1968) (Box 89, Folder 59)
    - 1969 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 89)
      - "Dinner #14," Der Scutt (Jan. 22, 1969) (Box 89, Folder 60)
      - "Dinner #15," Jordan Gruzen (Feb. 27, 1969) (Box 89, Folder 61)
      - "Dinner #16," Peace Corps (Mar. 26, 1969) (Box 89, Folder 62)
      - "Dinners for 36" #17, Robert A. Propper (Aug. 7, 1969) (Box 89, Folder 63)
    - 1969 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 90)
      - Julian C. Levi 95th Birthday Party (Dec. 5, 1969) (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Christmas Party (Dec. 22, 1969) (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - 1970 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 90)
      - 1970 Lecture Series: A-Z, 1969-1970; (8 folders) (Box 90, Folder 3-10)
      - 1970 Lecture Series, Lists, General Correspondence, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - 1970 Lecture Series, Suzanne Stephens, 1970-1971 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - Christmas Party (Dec. [22?], 1970) (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - 1971 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 90)
      - Luncheon (Nov. 10, 1971) (Box 90, Folder 14)
      - Cooper Union Lecture at MoMA (Nov. 12-13, 1971) (Box 90, Folder 15)
      - Charles Eames Film Program (Dec. 15, 1971, 8-10:30pm) (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - Christmas Party (Dec. 22, 1971) (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - 1972 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 90)
      - Cocktail Party for New Members (Jan. 10, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 18)
      - MacDonald Becket Lecture (Jan. 25, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 19)
      - Evenings Out: Earl Ruback, Waddell Gallery (Feb. 2, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 20)
      - "Dinners for 36, #23" (Feb. 17, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 21)
      - Evenings Out: Hans Namuth (Mar. 8, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 22)
      - Horace Hayden Lecture (Mar. 21, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 23)
      - Evenings Out: Helene Aylon, Max Hutchinson Gallery (Apr. 11, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 24)
      - Robert Gerson Lecture (Apr. 18, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 25)
      - Peter Blake Lecture (Apr. 26, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 26)
      - John Portman Dinner (Sept. 28, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 27)
      - Lecture Series on Industrialized Building (Oct. 11, 18 and 25, 1972, 8:30pm) (Box 90, Folder 28)
      - "Dinners for 36, #24," Angkor (Nov. 15, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 29)
      - Christmas Party (Dec. 21, 1972) (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - 1973 League-Sponsored Functions and Events (Box 90)
      - California Lecture: Ghery, Follis, Diniz (Apr. 1973) (Box 90, Folder 31)
      - Lectures: Film Event (w/MAS) (June 14, 1973) (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - 50th Anniversary Banquet, Details of [P?] (Apr. 24, 1931), (Oversized materials from Box 84, Folder 2) (Box OV 120)
  - Functions and Events Sponsored by Others, 1941-1966; 6.2
    The Architectural League of New York provided rental space in the League building to other organizations or individuals for their events and functions. Found in this subseries is correspondence, lists, printed materials, receipts, and other materials. The bulk of the material is from the 1950s-1960s. Generally, folder titles were transcribed from the original folder titles; however, event dates and additional descriptive information may have been added if the processing archivist was able to determine correct information from the folder materials.
    - League of Life Insurance Women, 1941-1942 (Box 90, Folder 33)
    - Beaux-Arts Institute of Design (B.A.I.D.), 1942-1943 (Box 90, Folder 34)
    - Irving B. Simon, McFadden Publications, Dinners, 1943-1945 (Box 90, Folder 35)
    - Task Magazine, 1943 (Box 90, Folder 36)
    - American Museum of Natural History Dinner, 1944 (Box 90, Folder 37)
    - Quiet Birdmen, 1946 (Box 90, Folder 38)
    - Mr. Cheek's Party (Dec. 5, 1946) (Box 90, Folder 39)
    - Quiet Birdmen, 1947-1949 (Box 90, Folder 40)
    - Columbia University School of Architecture Dinner (May 28, 1947) (Box 90, Folder 41)
    - M.I.T. Dinner, 1949 (Box 90, Folder 42)
    - Young Women's Republican Club Dinner, 1949 (Box 90, Folder 43)
    - 1950 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 90)
      - American Institute of Architects Luncheons, 1950-1953 (Box 90, Folder 44)
      - M.I.T. Dinners, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 45)
      - Phi Kappa Psi Luncheons, Pine Room, 1950-1952 (Box 90, Folder 46)
      - Quiet Birdmen Monday Evening Dinners, Dining Room, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 47)
      - Syracuse University Alumni Luncheon, Gallery "A", 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 48)
      - Typophiles, 1950-1956 (Box 90, Folder 49)
      - Edward Fischer Cocktail Party (Mar. 31, 1950) (Box 90, Folder 50)
      - Type Directors Club Dinner (Apr. 28, 1950) (Box 90, Folder 51)
      - Municipal Art Society Luncheon Meetings, Pine Room (Oct. 23, Nov. 20, Dec. 18, 1950) (Box 90, Folder 52)
      - Wine Tasting Party, Dining Room (Oct. 26, 1950) (Box 90, Folder 53)
      - Producers' Council Luncheon, Pine Room (Nov. 15, 1950), 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 54)
      - Fine Arts Federation of New York Luncheon, Gallery "A" (Nov. 28, 1950) (Box 90, Folder 55)
      - Architect's Emergency Committee Luncheon, Gallery "A" (Dec. 7, 1950) (Box 90, Folder 56)
      - Ralph Walker Dinner, Pine Room (Dec. 7, 1950) (Box 90, Folder 57)
      - Art Directors Christmas Party, Gallery "A" (Dec. 13, 1950, 5pm) (Box 90, Folder 58)
      - Eldredge Snyder Luncheon, Pine Room (Dec. 15, 1950) (Box 90, Folder 59)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company Cocktail Party, Gallery "A" (Dec. 15, 1950) (Box 90, Folder 60)
      - Wallace K. Harrison Christmas Party, Gallery "A" (Dec. 20, 1950, 12:30pm) (Box 90, Folder 61)
      - Voorhees, Walker, Foley and Smith Christmas Party, Gallery "A" (Dec. 22, 1950) (Box 90, Folder 62)
      - American Society of Landscape Architects Luncheon Meeting, Pine Room (Dec. 28, 1950, 12:30pm) (Box 90, Folder 63)
    - 1951 Functions and Events Sponsored by Others (Box 90)
      - American Institute of Graphic Arts, 1951-1952 (Box 90, Folder 64)